已經早上了嗎
Is it morning already?
傑瑞得
Jarrod...
傑瑞得  醒醒
Jarrod, wake up.
別怕
It's okay.
這是怎麼回事
What is that?
不知道
I don't know.
雷
Ray!
待這別動
Stay here.
怎麼回事
What's wrong?
他被吸走了
He's gone!
傑瑞得  傑瑞得
Jarrod! Jarrod!
回來啊
Come here.
傑瑞得
Jarrod.
15小時之前
我選不出來
I can't decide.
伊戀  你來選最後一張吧
Elaine, you pick the last one.
傑愛樂  泰愛財
Jay-rock... T-money...
我們那時候意識太超前  倆壞小子
Oh, we were...ahead of our time, we were bad.
你真是一點沒變
You haven't changed a bit.
泰瑞也是
Neither has Terry...
你馬上就能見到了
You'll see.
他是個棒小夥
He's a real deal.
迫不及待了
Can't wait.
愛德華  你拍那個爛片之前
Edward you should thought about that
就應該想清楚
before you shot that piece of shit.
你這麼早在這幹什麼
What you doing here so early?
-今天天不錯  -我也知道
- It's a beautiful day. - Don't I know it.
巴瑞問關於機器人系列的事
Barry called in about the robot
告訴他  讓他自己搞定
Tell him, handle it.
今天我生日  不談公事
No business on my birthday.
-寶貝  -她非得天天待這嗎
- Babe.  - God, she always has to be here?
這是她的工作
She's working.
沒辦法
So pathetic.
走開  你一身汗
You're sweaty.
-伊戀  你還好吧  -還好
- Elaine. Are you alright  - Yeah.
沒事  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我來幫你拿  給
Here, let me get that for you. Here you go.
-謝謝  -不用謝
- Thank you.  - No Problem.
這才是我的偶像
That's my hero.
-傑愛樂  -奧唐納
- "J" - Rock. - O'DONNELL
好吧  就是我們
Yeah, that... that's us.
開什麼玩笑
Oh, you gotta be kidding me!
你最好別搞習慣這種待遇了
You better not get used to this.
我嗎
Who? Me?
頂層公寓
Penthouse.
到了  走吧
Alright. Come on.
你這個千年老二混得怎樣啊
How the second most talented guy I know?
不清楚  你呢
I don't know, how are you?
我很好
I'm good.
生日快樂
Happy Birthday!
想必你就是伊戀吧  歡迎
Oh... You must be Elaine?
-對  -歡迎
- Yeah.  - Welcome.
這裡棒極了
This is amazing.
這裡全是自動化的設備
Automatic even at its finest.
是我在雲端的私人空間
My own personal place in the clouds.
這的景致實在是太棒了
The view is incredible.
我有個問題想問你
Let me ask you a question.
我哥們給你添麻煩了嗎
You keeping my boy in line?
不許回答
Don't answer that... hey!
看著他可是我的全職工作
It's a full time job.
不管他付你多少  我都給你雙倍
Whatever he is paying you, I'll double it.
看起來你已經夠忙的了
Oh, well, looks like, you got your hands full already.
說得好
I like that. Yeah.
你們的房間在那
That's your room right here.
想去泳池嗎
You guys wanna hit the pool?
那還用說
Absolutely.
寶貝
Babe!
游泳時間
Pool Time!
-寶貝  幫我拿杯柯夢  -好  拿著這個
- Baby, get me a cosmo. - Absolutely, hold this.
吧台在這邊
Hey, the bar's this way.
-哥們  你真的做到了  -沒錯
- You really did it, man.  - Yeah.
這的人幾乎都認識你  但是...
I mean just like everybody knew you would, but...
帥哥們
Hey, guys.
你好美女
Hello...
沒有你  我做不到這些
I wouldn't have done without you.
我做了什麼  幫你刷牆嗎
What I do? Decorate the walls?
-你看起來不錯  -你也是
- You do look nice. - And you do look nice.
生日快樂  泰瑞
Happy Birthday, Terry.
沒錯  祝我生日快樂
Yeah, happy birthday to me.
我簡直不能想像
I can't think of all this man,
我不知道送你點什麼好
And I do not know what to give you as a gift.
我有個主意
I got some ideas on that.
跟我來
Come on.
大家貌似聊得很開心啊
I see everyone getting along famously.
-寶貝  -在
- Baby?  - Yeah?
我的柯夢呢
Where is my cosmo?
我的錯
Owh, my bad.
鄧尼斯  幫我去拿
Denise, get me a drink.
-其他人要嗎  -不用
- Anyone else? - No.
這比12月的布魯克林好多了
Well, this definitely beats Brooklyn in December.
我倒還是挺喜歡咱們分明的四季
I don't know, I kinda like our four Seasons.
四季啊  我們這街那頭就有家四季酒店
We got one of those, down the block.
明天  咱們駕著
Tomorrow we're gonna hit the high sea,
我的逐日號出海去
I'm gonna take you all out on my Sunseeker.
船身有二十米  爽翻了
It's a 67 footer.
是國土安全局的
That's Homeland Security.
他們來這兒  肯定是知道
They must be here because they know
今晚將有一場爆炸性的派對
tonights party is gonna be a "bomb".
乾杯
Cheers.
生日快樂  泰瑞
Happy Birthday, Terry!
-哥們  最近咋樣  -不錯
- Oh hi, dude. How's it going man? - I'm alright.
我想介紹個人給你  雷
There's somebody I want you to meet. Ray!
等我下
Hold on.
-生日快樂  哥們  -謝謝
- Well, birthday boy, happy Birthday, man. - Thank you.
"機器人大戰"  進展如何了
How's the "robot fight" coming along?
爛死了  但那些人喜歡  所以你懂的
Dude, it's sucks, but the director loves it, so... you know.
-這就是你說的那人  -對
- Hey, is this the boy wonder? - Yeah.
還有他漂亮的女友
And his lovely lady, yeah.
-很高興認識你  哥們  -我也是
- Hey, good to meet you, man. - Yeah.
我很高興  你能加入我們的團隊
Listen, I'm psyched you're gonna join the crew.
什麼  我
Huh?... I mean, I...
你找到住的地方了嗎
Hey, hey, did you find a place to live yet?
威尼斯  就在那個美麗的地方
I'm telling you, Venice, it's where it's at.
-我們住那  -我們有地方住  謝謝
- I live there, so...  - We have a place, thank you.
也是
Sure you have.
-我去下洗手間  -好
- I have to go to the little girl's room. - Alright.
-失陪一下  -等等
- Excuse me. - No...
寶貝  伊戀
Babe... Elaine!
她真漂亮  哥們福氣不淺啊
She's smokin', nice job dude.
-等會聊  我們得走了  -他說什麼啊
- Wait up for me. Let's go. - What's he talking about?
美女玩得怎樣了
What's going on, ladies?
-不好意思  -到底怎麼回事
- Sorry. - What was that all about?
聽著
Hey, look.
看來紙包不住火了
The cat's obviously outta the bag...
我在想
I was thinking...
你搬來洛杉磯吧
you should move to L.A.
我在這能做什麼  我是說
What am I gonna do out here? I mean...
我在老家還有工作呢
I rather survive back home.
我可以雇你
I could use you.
我不要你的施捨
Oh, I don't need any charity, alright?
好吧
Okay fine.
我需要你
I need you.
哥們  我對那些玩意一無所知
I don't know anything about effects, man.
-別胡扯了  -我沒扯
- That's bullshit, come on. - That's not bullshit.
你知道你有這個天賦的
You got the eye and you know it.
電腦只是個工具
Alright...Computer is just a tool.
我不知道  我從來沒想過要來這裡工作
I don't know, okay? I never saw myself out here.
那你覺得自己應該做什麼
Where do you see yourself?
你還有個五年計劃嗎
You got five year plan I don't know about?
這跟錢沒關係
It's not about the money, okay?
我們就是為了賺錢
It's always about the money.
那伊戀怎麼辦
What about Elaine?
我沒法顧及所有事  你得自己解決
I can't handle everything. You gotta take care of that yourself.
泰瑞  前臺有電話找你
Terry, there's a call for you upstairs.
你考慮下吧
You think about it.
伊戀
Elaine.
別哭了
Come on.
我們是來度假的  怎麼回事
We are supposed to be having fun, what is the problem?
別問了
Just forget it, alright?
聽著
Look...
泰瑞今天才把所有事告訴我
Terry sprung this whole California thing on me today, alright?
-我也不知道...  -有點晚了
- I had no idea, I didn't... - I'm late.
什麼晚了
What you mean, late?
那個
Late...
不好意思  抱歉
Oh, excuse me...Sorry.
多久了
Since when?
我不知道
I don't know.
最近一直覺得很噁心  所以我做了個測試  然後
I've been feeling sick all week, so I took a test and...
為什麼不告訴我
Why didn't you tell me?
相信我  我想告訴你的
I wanted to... Believe me,
只是  不想破壞你的旅行
I just...I didn't wanna ruin your trip.
操
Shit.
這就是你想說的嗎
Is that all you have to say?
那你想讓我說什麼
What do you want me to say?
-我壓根沒準備好  -你沒準備好  傑瑞得
- I don't think I'm ready for this. - You're not ready, Jarrod?
那我呢
What about me?
這不是  你能不能別再
It's not...hey, will you keep...
這是我們必須面對的
Is that what we have to look forward too.
戀妮
Leni...
快  快  快  快  快
Hey man, we got... we got a lot... lot more.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
快  快  快  快  快
Go... go... go...go... go...
我的老天
Oh, my God, man!
女士  很不好意思
Pardon me ma'am, but...
我們收到些雜訊投訴
we received a few noise complaints.
誰投訴啊
From whom?
這樓一半都空著
The building's half empty.
我明白  但是另一半住戶需要休息
I understand that, but...the other half is trying to sleep.
-如果您不介意的話  -好吧
- So, if you don't mind if you just... - Alright.
我也要上來
Another one for the books.
沙發是我的
I got the couch.
別啊  這地方足夠咱倆待了
Oh, come on, I think there's space for both of us?
-我需要空間  -好吧
- I like space. - Whoa, alright.
求人的沒得選啊
Beggers can't be chooser.
晚安
Good night.
第一天  淩晨4:27
地震了
Earthquake!
你做夢吧
You're probably just dreaming.
快把燈關了
Turn off the lights.
雷  你在幹什麼
Ray...What're you doing?
雷
Ray!
待這別動
Stay here.
-怎麼回事  -他被吸走了
- What's wrong? - He's gone.
傑瑞得  不
Jarrod, no.
不  傑瑞得
No, Jarrod, no.
傑瑞得  別過去
Jarrod... no.
怎麼了
What's going on, man?
傑瑞得  別過去
Jarrod, please stop.
醒醒  你怎麼了
What's with you, man?
傑瑞得
Jarrod?
天哪  傑瑞得
Oh, my God, Jarrod.
傑瑞得
Jarrod!
快醒醒  發生了什麼
Please..What's happening?
-傑瑞得  -天哪
- Jarrod.. - Oh God.
傑瑞得
Jarrod...
他怎麼了
What's wrong with him?
傑瑞得  老天啊
Jarrod? Oh my God.
-雷呢  雷去哪兒了  -別  別過去
- Where's Ray? Where's Ray? - No, no, no, no...
-傑瑞得  -他去哪了
- Jarrod.  - Where is he?
-被吸走了  -什麼意思
- He's gone! - What do you mean he's gone?
-就是被吸走了  -掉下去了
- I mean, he's gone! - Did he fall?
-沒有  -跳下去了嗎
- No. - Did he jump?
沒有  我不知道
No! I don't...
他看著那光  然後走過去
He went outside...to the light.
然後就  就消失了
And then he...he just disappeared.
泰瑞
Terry...
泰瑞  求你了  別過去
Terry, please!
你剛才看見什麼了  看見什麼了
What did you see? What did you see?
小心
Be careful
傑瑞得  到底怎麼回事
Jarrod, what happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
我被吸向那道光
I was being pulled...towards this light.
-把百葉窗拉起來  -不
- Open the blinds. - No.
-拉起來  -不
- Open the blinds! - No!
媽的
Goddamn it...
下面好像有什麼東西
There's something down there.
什麼
What?
傑瑞得  過來看看
Jarrod, check this out.
我什麼也沒看見
I don't see anything.
-房頂上有人  -他們在幹什麼
- There are people on roof. - What are they doing?
看不清
I don't know.
我們該去看看
We should check it out.
你不知道外面那是什麼
You don't know what's out there.
-我沒事  -好吧
- I'll be okay. - Alright.
我去報警
I'm calling the police.
-我去拍點照  -你還不能出去
- I'll try to take some pictures. - You can't go out there.
我不是一個人去
I'm not going out there alone.
沒人接電話
It just keeps ringing.
你要帶著槍
A gun?
有用嗎
Really?
你注意看新聞  搞清楚到底怎麼回事
Just check the news and find out what the hell's going on.
-泰瑞  -我們馬上就回來
- Terry..  - We'll be right back.
-傑瑞得  -看著我
- Jarrod.  - Look at me.
出發吧
Let's go.
快去快回
Hurry back.
樓梯在這邊
The stairs are this way.
怎麼了
What's going on?
我要去看看
I'm going to check it out.
你們拿槍做什麼
What're you doing with the gun?
快回你的房間去  快
Get back in your apartment. Go!
別出聲
And keep it down.
確定要這麼做嗎
Hey...you sure about this?
確定
Yeah.
從淩晨四點開始  就沒有更新新聞了
There's been nothing new since 4 am.
丹妮斯  去看下電視
Denise, check the TV.
很平靜
It's calm.
操  傑瑞得
Damn it, Jarrod.
你沒告訴我要留門
You didn't tell me to hold it open.
這不是常識嗎
I thought it was common sense.
對不起
I'm sorry.
蹲下
Get down.
現在怎麼辦
What now?
走近點看看
Let's get a better look.
這是傑姬的電話  請留言
Hi, this is Jackie. Please leave a message.
媽  是我
Mom, it's me.
有事發生了  接電話啊
Something happened and...pick up.
拜託  聽到後  快回我電話
Please, just...call me back as soon as you get this.
天殺的
Holy shit.
-我看不清  -是咱們想的那樣嗎
- I can't see it. - Is that what I think it is?
蒼天啊
My God.
-快跑  -那是什麼
- Just Run!  - What is it?
-跑  -快跑
Run! Let's go.
快跑
Go!
使勁
Come on, pull!
讓開  退後
Back up! Back up!
使勁
Come on!
伊戀  不
Elaine, no!
讓開  讓開
Move... move!
親愛的  你還好嗎
Baby, are you okay?
我覺得我著火了
I feel like I'm on fire.
看著我
Look at me...
你也看見了
You look it too.
怎麼回事
How?
我的老天啊
Oh, my God!
那麼多人都被吸走了
All those people.
他們到底想幹什麼
What they want with them?
我可不想再上去了
I'm not gonna go find out.
簡直不敢相信  這怎麼可能
God, can't believe this...I mean how?...
你一旦看到那光
Once you look at the light...
它就會抓住你  就好像
It grabs hold. It's like that...
被它控制一樣
It controls you.
誰不想看到如此神奇的東西
I mean, who wouldn't wanna look at something so beautiful?
看上去確實很美
It's kinda brilliant, actually.
別說廢話了
Enough of this shit.
我想到個主意
I got an idea.
你去哪兒
Where you going?
-去沃特家  -泰瑞  -去幹什麼
- Walt's.  - Terry?  - What for?
-別擔心  -泰瑞
Don't worry about it.
-泰瑞  -一切都在我掌握之中
- Terry? - Everything's under control.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
沒事
Yeah, it's nothing.
讓我看下
Let me see.
我說沒事了
I said its nothin'.
好吧
Alright.
沃特
Walt?
Yo... Walt?
沃特
Walt?
你在嗎
Are you in here?
你他媽的在這裡幹什麼
What the hell you doing?
躲著
Hiding.
我看見人們飛向空中
I saw the people in the sky...
天空他媽的就像裂了一道縫
like the Goddamn rapture.
快點  我們開你的車
Come on, we're taking your car,
離開這裡  走吧
we're getting the hell outta here. Lets go!
我是不會出去的
I'm not going out there!
趴下  趴下
Get down!
讓那狗別叫了  讓那狗別叫了
Shut the dog up, shut the dog up!
-不  -別  不要
- Oh, God no...  - No... no...
沃特
Walt!
你聽見了嗎
Did you hear that?
怎麼了
Talk to me.
咱們去我的船上  趕緊離開這裡
We need to get my boat and gettin' outta here.
發生什麼事了
What happened?
它們吸走了沃特
They took Walt.
沃特被吸走了  你說什麼呢
They took Walt? What're you talking about?
這次情形不一樣  他們闖進樓裡
This one was different. They came in the building
把他吸走了
and they just snatched him.
我們快走吧
Then we just go.
等一下
Hold on a sec.
你們難道沒看照片嗎
Am I the only one who saw these photos?
這一切就發生在外面  近在眼前
It's all happening right outside, right now. They're everywhere.
它們無處不在  它們
But they're not everywhere. They're...
水上沒有那些東西
they're not over the water.
他說得對
He's right.
在屋頂上
Yeah, well, it didn't take 'em very long
它們很快就找到你了
to find who you on the roof.
兩分鐘就到了
We can drive there in 2 minutes.
你不知道它們會怎樣
You have no idea what they are capable of.
我知道你很害怕  我們都害怕
Ellie, I know you are scared, okay? We're all scared.
但我不會只畏首畏尾地坐在這祈禱它們離開的
But I'm not burying my head in the sand, hoping it goes away.
-我可沒這麼說  -放輕鬆
- I'm not saying that. - Look, just take it easy, man.
-它們不會慢慢來  -我知道它們不會
- It's not easy with all this... - I know it's not.
它們就在這該死的樓裡
They're in the fucking building.
泰瑞
Terry?
計時器
It's the timer.
我的天啊
My God.
快走  走  走
Go... go... move...move!
你真噁心
You're disgusting!
你到底有什麼毛病啊
What the hell's the matter with you?
-我們待會再談那個  -沒錯  待會談
- We'll talk about that later. - Yeah, we will talk about that.
-還想留下來嗎  -我什麼也不想
- You still wanna stay?  - I don't want... any of this.
它們沒看見我們  所以我們就待在這裡  安靜待著
They didn't see us so we stay here and stay quiet.
那要待多久呢
For how long?
它們就這樣把人吸走  易如反掌
They're taking people out there, plain and simple.
我們跑得越遠就越安全
The further we get outta the city, the better off we are.
他說的沒錯
He's right.
傑瑞得
Jarrod.
如果能上船  我們就還有一線生機
If we get to the boat we have a chance!
-對  但是咱們  -我們
- Yeah, but if we don't... - We have...
必須試試
We have to try.
我們只帶水和食物
We just, get food and water.
行動吧
Let's do this.
好了  快點
Alright, come on.
聽著  我越早過去
Look, the sooner I get there,
船就越早能走
the sooner the boat's ready to go.
去哪
Where
-快點  我們走  -什麼
- Come on, let's go. - What..
你幹什麼呢
What you doing?
開車  我認識路  你就帶好你的小三吧
Driving, I know the way! You just take your slut.
坎蒂絲
Candice...
Candice.
上車
Get in the car!
泰瑞  對不起
Terry, I'm sorry.
-快點  -我也想快點
- Hurry up.  - What do you think I'm doing?
-停一下  -沒門
- Hey, slow down. - No.
給我停下
Just stop!
需要幫忙嗎
You need any help?
-不用了  我們沒事  -但是  也許
- No, go, we're fine. - Yeah but, maybe...
打住  我說過沒事了
Enough, alright? I said, we're fine.
泰瑞  快起來  快跑
Terry, get up! Run!
快
Come on.
泰瑞  泰瑞
Hey, Terry...Terry!
傑瑞得  回車上來
Jarrod! Get your ass back here now!
快回來
Back up!
快
Come on.
-開門啊  見鬼  -快點
- Open! Oh shit. - Come on.
開啊
Open!
快開
Come on.
快開啊  這坨屎
Open, you piece of shit!
退回去  退回去  退回去
Back up! Back up! Back up!
我的天哪  救救我
Oh, my God. Help me!
來人啊  救我
Someone help!
-咱們得離開這  -把鑰匙給我
- We gotta get outta here. - Give me the keys.
你沒事吧
You alright?
他沒事
He's fine.
天啊
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
-小姐你必須離開這裡...  -不要
- Miss, we have to go... - No.
他還活著
He's alive!
科林
Colin!
幫幫我
Help me!
快點  我們走
Come on, let's go!
走  走
Go! Go!
往後門跑
Make it to the back door.
跑啊
Run!
快
Go!
別停
Don't stop!
開門
Open the door!
快點
Hurry!
-閃開  -打開它
- Get it open. - Back up.
快開
Open it.
我們去哪
Where we going?
我能想到的最安全的地方就是樓頂
All the way to the top is the safest place I can think of.
它要是在那怎麼辦
What if they're up there?
如果你想坐在這裡  就請便
If you wanna stay out here with them, be my guest.
快點  我們走
Come on, let's go.
快  快  快
Come on, quickly... quickly...quickly!
過來幫我一把
Hey!...Come help me with this.
總比什麼都沒有強吧
It's better than nothing, right?
隨你怎麼說
Yeah, if you say so.
你什麼意思啊
What're you doing, huh?
木已成舟  由不得你了
Like it or not, this is happening.
你得堅強點
You gotta be strong.
大家都好吧
Is everybody okay?
你受傷了嗎
Are you hurt?
-沒有  -我沒事
- No...  - I'm okay.
-現在怎麼辦呢  -待在這
- What now?  - We stay here...
繼續觀察同時祈禱有人來救我們
We keep watch and we pray that someone comes.
他說的對
He's right.
有人會來救我們
Someone's gonna come.
不可能一直就這樣下去
This can't go on forever.
是吧
Right?
小姐  我們最好待在一起
Sweety, it's best if we stay together.
我沒辦法
I can't...
二手煙...
the smoke.
在這種情況下  抽根煙再正常不過了吧
Given such circumstances, I think a smoke is more than reasonable.
坎蒂絲...
Candice...
我懷孕了  號碼
I'm pregnant, alright?
發生了這麼多事
And I just thought that...
我這才反應上來
that with all this stress...
沒事
It's okay.
我得告訴我媽一聲
Jarrod, I got to tell my mom.
來吧  老大
Come on, boss.
讓她們睡會兒
Let's let the girls get some sleep.
我們放哨
You and I will keep watch now.
我們兩個都留下嗎
Both of us?
它們要用強光那一套  我們也好有個照應
They try that light stuff, we got each others back.
我討厭洛杉磯
I hate L.A.
整晚連個影子都沒看見
I haven't seen a soul all night.
可能最糟的已經過去了吧
Maybe the worst is over.
可能還沒
Maybe not.
你覺得它們究竟是什麼呢
What do you think these things really are?
不知道
I don't know.
現在這還重要嗎
Does it even matter?
這一切就像幻覺
It just doesn't seem real.
這不是幻覺
Well, it is real.
你最好清醒些
You better wake up.
你那話什麼意思
What's that supposed to mean?
整個城市都空了
The city is a vacant lot.
我們必須活下來
We need to survive.
活下來的人不會不會太多
There's not gonna be many of us left.
你看見什麼了
What do you see?
有人在反擊
Somebody is fighting back.
-你要幹什麼  -看看外面發生什麼事了
- What're you doing? - I wanna see what's out there.
把顯示器關了  它太亮了
Turn that off, its too bright.
-不  -我們不能冒這個險
- No! - We can't risk it.
你一夜沒睡嗎
Did you sleep at all?
情況更糟了嗎
Is it getting worse?
-什麼  -你皮膚上那些印記
- What? - The marks on your skin.
看著那束光  我堅持不了十分鐘
When I looked into that light, I couldn't stand for 10 minutes.
誰知道那東西究竟對我們做了什麼
Who knows what it did to us...
對我們身體有什麼影響
to our bodies.
你還記得看見那東西的最開始
You remember the first moment when you saw it?
當它徹底占了上風
When it completely took over?
不知怎麼  你也感覺自己充滿了
Somehow you...you still felt...
力量
powerful.
我現在仍有這種感覺
I still do.
你坐下來休息一會兒吧
Why don't you take a seat...relax.
好吧  我就聽聽看
Alright, I'll bite.
有什麼計畫  你一定迫不及待想告訴我
What's your plan boss, 'cause I know you're dying to tell me.
沒什麼要說的嗎
Nothing to say?
我們就在港口附近
We're sitting on a marina for Chirst sakes...
這我知道
I've noticed that.
穿過街道就有成百上千條船停著
There are hundreds of boats right across the street.
咱們嘗試過
We've been through all this.
提醒大家一下上次你們結局如何啊
Remind us how that was done last time?
這次我們悄悄過去
We... we go quietly this time.
然後搜遍每條船去找鑰匙嗎
And search every boat 'till we find a key?
-我們沒得選擇  -真是好計畫  傑瑞得
- If we have to... - Great plan, Jarrod.
不敢相信在經歷了這一切之後你堅持那麼做
I can't believe you even suggest that, after what happened.
那難道是我的錯嗎
Are you saying it was my fault?
我當時幾乎是在求你  但你就是不聽
I was practically begging, but you wouldn't listen.
那你認為泰瑞會聽我的嗎
And you think that Terry wouldn't listen me?
夠了
Alright...
就算我們走出這棟樓
Let's say we make it outta the building.
穿過小港到了碼頭
Across the marina down the dock.
我們找到船  然後呢
We even find a boat and everything, then what?
-離開碼頭  -去哪裡
- We get the hell outta Dodge. - Where to?
到卡羅萊納州嗎  順海岸往下走嗎
Carolina, down the coast?
-任何地方都比這裡強  -你怎麼知道
- Anywhere is better than here! - How do you know?
我們待在這
We're here.
最起碼還活著
We're alive.
什麼聲音啊
What was that?
看見什麼了
What do you see?
上帝顯靈了
Hallelujah.
加油  加油  加油
Come on... come on...come on!
都趴下
Everybody get down!
戀妮
Leni?
成功了
It worked.
-簡直不敢相信  -結束了嗎
- I don't believe it. - Is it over?
-我能看看嗎  -請便  老大
- Do you mind? - By all means, boss.
你覺得會有更多飛機飛過來嗎
Do you think there're more planes where they came from?
會的  現在他們知道怎麼對付它們了
Yes, now they know what to do.
他們會即刻發出救援的
They'll be sending help in no time.
怎麼了
What?
發生什麼事了
What is it?
那東西沒死
They're not dead.
它們徹底被惹毛了
They're just really...really pissed off.
情況有變
Something is happening.
必須把所有窗戶都遮起來
We have to cover these windows.
過來幫我一把
Come help me with this.
給我回來
Get back over here!
我去找些東西
I'll find something.
給
Here.
傑瑞得  你幹什麼
Jarrod, what are you doing?
它們要過來了
They'll be coming here.
你究竟在幹什麼
What's this really about, huh?
那些東西在四處尋找我們
Those things are coming for us.
你覺得我沒注意到你襯衫下的印記嗎
You think I haven't noticed that mess under your shirt?
我們待在這裡  堅持住
We stay here and hold up...for good.
我同意
I agree.
那我看事情就那樣了吧  沒水了
Well, I guess that said everything, we have no water.
-沒電  -是  但你看清楚外面什麼情況
- No power..  - Yeah, but you saw what's out there.
看見了  但我寧願一試
Yeah, but I would rather make a run for it,
也好過留在這二十樓高的地方等死
than stay in a 20 story target.
在那些東西和放射的夾擊下  我們必死無疑
Between those things and the radiaton, we are dead up here.
快快快  駐守抵抗
Go... go... go... go, let's make a stand.
-放開我  -你他媽以為自己做什麼呢
- Let go off me!  - What the hell do you think you're doing?
-讓他們知道咱們在這  -不准出去
- To let them know we are here.  - We'll let everything go!
是誰說要等救援的  現在救援就在外面
I'm saying we call for help. The help is here.
你看那像救援飛機嗎
Does that look like a rescue chopper to you?
還不明白嗎  這是一場戰爭
Don't you get it? We're at war.
那飛機怎麼走了呢
Where are they going?
直升機會回來接他們的  我們得走了
Those choppers are coming back for them. We have to go.
快點
Come on.
我們去樓頂  他們會接我們的
We get to the roof. They'll pick us up.
萬一飛機不回來了呢
What if they don't come back?
看看它們對這些飛機都做了什麼
Look what they did to those planes.
直升飛機還比不上那些飛機呢
What good is a helicopter?
-我們必須冒險一試  -冒險嗎
- We have to take a chance. - A chance?
那些東西剛剛廢了整個城市  你現在還想出去呼救
They just nuked the city, and you wanna wave hello?
你閃一邊去  我們沒得選擇...
I just need you to back off. We have to try...
見鬼
Oh shit.
你就準備那麼站著嗎
You just gonna stand there?
如果大廈垮塌了怎麼辦
What happens when the rest of the blocks fall?
我們連擋窗戶的床單都沒有
We really don't have enough bed sheets.
-快  我們走  -你怎麼這麼肯定
- Come on. - How can you be so sure?
走就對了
Let's just go!
你沒權利決定任何事情
You're in no condition to decide anything.
誰知道你現在站哪邊啊
Who knows what side you're on.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
住手  你們兩個
Stop it! Both of you!
看看他的臉吧
Look at his face.
他已經不正常了
He's sick.
-別讓我對你出手  -用不著你擔心
- Don't make me hurt you. - Oh, don't worry.
我是不會一個人離開的
I'm not leaving without my family.
你別想阻止我們
There is nothing, that you can do to stop us.
伊戀  你要相信我
Elaine, you have to trust me.
是我啊
It's me.
我還是...我
It's still...me.
我知道
I know.
咱們得走了
We have to go.
-他會害死咱們的  -快點
- He's gonna get us killed. - Come on.
走吧
Come on.
好了  我們走
Alright, lets go.
看見人沒
You see anyone?
就在那邊
They're right there.
-救救我們  -救救我們
- Help. - Help us!
不許動
Don't move!
-別開槍  -別開槍  等等
- Don't shoot.  - No, no, wait
-待在原地別動  -請救救我們
- Stay where you are!  - We need help, please.
不是吧  不  不
No... no... no!
不要...
No!...
快...
Come on!
-收到  -那邊兩人需要支援  去保護他們
Roger that, I see two people in shelter, go get them...
-這裡...喂  -喂
- Hey... hey... hey!...  - Hey!
不
No!...
快跑
Come on.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
傑羅得
Jarrod...
快跑  快跑  快跑
Go... go... go!
腳手架  那是唯一的出路  快  快過去
The scaffold... it's the only way down. Come on, go!
戀妮  快跑
Leni, run!
操
Fuck!
一路走好  你個臭婊子養的
Vaya con Dios you son of a bitch!
救命  救救我
Help me! Help.
救我...
Help me...
傑瑞得  看著我
Jarrod. Look, look at me.
看著我  傑瑞得
Look at me, Jarrod.
站起來  快
Get up. Come on.
我看見它了
I saw the way it is
戀妮  快
Leni, please.
你快逃吧
You have to go.
沒有你我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere without you.
第三天
傑瑞得
Jarrod!
我的孩子
My baby!
傑瑞得
Jarrod...